My takeaway from today are the interchangeable terms such as first premolar and first bicuspid.
My takeaway from today was that you purge your water and air line for 20 to 30 seconds
between patients.
My takeaway from today is that you don't sanitize your room, you disinfect it.
Is that you must use one hand to recap the needle.
My takeaway from today is understanding where to put the topical anesthesia on the maxillary
arch and the mandibular arch.
My takeaway so far is every tooth has a mesial and a distal surface.
My biggest takeaway is that wearing gloves when cleaning a room means you're dirty.
My takeaway from today was learning how to recap with the one hand scoop technique and
then from last class it was learning the surfaces of the teeth.
My takeaway from today was learning how to sterilize instruments.
My biggest takeaway is that you use the blue needle for the maxillary and then you use
the yellow needle for the mandibular.